Another big piece of the user experience are notifications.
用户体验另外一个重要的部分是通知
Notifications allow you to communicate with the user,
通过通知 你可以与用户进行沟通
and they can take many different forms, text messages, emails,
通知有很多形式 例如短信、电邮
push notifications, icons, vibrations, banners, and alerts.
推送、标记、振动、横幅、警告
You'll need to think carefully about how often you notify users and
你应该认真考虑你通知用户的频率
what forms those notifications take,
以及通知的形式
since they contribute to the overall user experience.
因为这些都会影响整体的用户体验
A graph or matrix like this one can help you think through the importance and
这样的图表或矩阵能够帮你理清
urgency of your notifications.
通知的重要性和紧急性
As I walk through the upcoming examples, you should think about
在我带领大家学习实例时 你应该想想
where notifications might fall on this diagram.
通知应位于这张图的什么地方
In general, you want to avoid sending many messages that have low importance
总体来说 你需要避免发送很多
and low urgency.
重要性与紧急性都比较低的信息
If you're sending a lot of these types of messages,
如果你发送太多这种类型的信息
it can make your product feel spammy.
你的产品会被认为太具骚扰性
Keep in mind that the frequency for a given notification may change over time,
请记住 特定通知的频率可能会随时发生变更
and this graph might look different for different personas using the product.
本图表对使用产品的不同角色模型来说是不同的
You should think about different notifications for
在设计产品时 你应该考虑针对不同的角色模型
different personas as you work on your product.
发送不同的通知
Some might have preferences for one notification over others.
有的人可能会偏好某一个特定的通知
In general, there's some key qualities of notifications
总体来讲 你应该记住
that you should keep in mind for your users.
通知对用户来说有一些关键的品质
The first one is control.
首先是控制
And it's the most important thing that you want to give users.
这是你想给到用户的最重要的东西
Little Big Details is a website that showcases a lot of
Little Big Details 这个网站
awesome user experience.
展示了很多极好的用户体验
When it comes to control,
说到控制这方面
Foursquare in Apple gives users lots of control through menus like these.
苹果的 Foursquare 通过这样的菜单给用户很多的控制选择
The second is feedback.
第二是反馈
Other types of notifications involve informing the user
其他类型的通知包括为用户执行任务
about tasks that they are performing.
提供信息
This is really just about good design in user experience.
在这种情况下 用户体验的关键就是良好的设计
The feedback provided is dependent on the product.
提供的反馈由产品决定
And by providing great feedback, you can make users
通过提供很好的反馈 用户能够感受到
feel like you're looking out for them while making the product more usable.
你在留意他们的感受 让产品越来越好用
For example, Twitter will try and
比如说 如果你在 Twitter 两次发送同一条推特
provide feedback if you send the same tweet twice.
Twitter 就会试着提供反馈
Slack, a messaging app also provides great feedback to users.
Slack 这个信息交流应用也为用户提供很好的反馈
It provides a confirmation when sending a message
向不同时区的人所在的频道发送信息时
to a channel that has people in different time zones.
它会提供确认信息
And Amazon provides feedback about whether someone may have bought you
Amazon 也会给反馈 说明是否有人
an item on your Wish List.
为你购买了你愿望清单上面的物品
All of these notifications are related to feedback loops for
这些通知都与反馈圈相关
users to successfully complete tasks.
能帮助用户成功完成任务
The third is customization.
第三个是个性化
It's a more subtle aspect of notifications for your users.
这是用户通知中很微妙的一个方面
You might do this based on time, task, location or
你可以根据用户的时间、任务、地点
some other attribute that's tied to the user.
或其他一些属性实现个性化
Facebook for example, shows a different part of the world to users,
比如说 Facebook 会根据用户的地点
depending on the user's location.
为用户展示不同的世界
Finally, you can develop notifications that lead users to form a habit of using
最后 你可以通过通知的频率以及你给到的奖励
your product depending on the frequency and any rewards you might give them.
让用户形成使用你的产品的习惯
You can tap into what Nir Eyal describes as variable rewards.
你可以利用 Nir Eyal 说到的可变奖励
GitHub provides variable rewards to its users by showing a different Octocat
GitHub 向用户提供可变奖励
each time the user has no new notifications.
在用户每次阅读所有通知后它会显示不同的 Octocat
Tumblr sends emails with playful texts when a user follows someone or
当 Tumblr 的用户关注谁或者被谁关注时
when someone else follows that user.
它会发送一封好玩的邮件给用户
And, Coffee Meets Bagel, which is a dating application,
Coffee Meets Bagel 这个约会应用
uses digital currency to reward users for tapping into the dating app.
会在用户点进这个约会应用时给予用户数字货币的奖励
Each of these qualities contributes to the user experience and
这些品质都能大大地影响用户体验
their perception of your product.
以及他们对你的产品的想法